（上条(かみじょう)）
猟犬部隊(ハウンドドッグ)の木原数多(きはら あまた)は―
Kihara Amata of Hound Dog defeats Accelerator.
アクセラレータを圧倒
しかも その目的は
ラストオーダーの回収だった
His goal was to retrieve Last Order.
アクセラレータは
ラストオーダーを逃がすが
Accelerator allows Last Order to escape,
反撃の手だてはない　そこに…
but has no means of fighting back.
That's when...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）そこで何しているの？
（木原）ああ？
What do you think you're doing?
～♪
#20 Hound Dog
Hunting Dog Unit
（木原）チッ…
（隊員）どうしますか？
What should we do?
（木原）
ああ？　どうするって お前…
消すしかねえだろう
What else?
Make her disappear.
Drive.
進め
さっさと病院に行かねえと―
You're going to die if you don't get to a hospital soon.
手遅れになるぞ
（ｵｰｿﾝ）
ヒイッ…
What the hell are you doing?
（木原）
おい 何してる？　早く撃て
Shoot him!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
ウワッ！　アッ！
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん？
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）騒ぐんじゃねえぞ
Don't make a fuss.
And you, just keep going straight.
いいから直進しろ
時間がねえのは お互いさまだろう
We both don't have much time.
Wh-Where should we go?
ど… どちらまで？
I know a good doctor.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
いい医者を知ってるんだ
Ahh, man.
ああ ああ… あれだ あれ
あれ持ってこい！
Bring that thing over!
Give it here!
Come on.
（木原）
甘々だぜ
Being in a car is like having a big sign saying you can't control wind in there.
車なんか使っちまったら
風の操作は使えねえってのを―
アピールしてるような
もんじゃねえかよ
See you later, shithead.
（木原）
あばよ くそ野郎
Oh come on.
…たく
What a nice city.
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
いい街ね
I was thinking the corruption would move much faster.
もっと早く侵食が
進むもんだとばかり思ってたけど
Who the hell are you?
（木原）何者だ？
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）殺しの商売敵
Your business rival in hitman services.
ハァ… 殺せ
Kill her.
You don't consider me a threat, do you?
あんた 敵意がないのね
If you want me to, then get a little better at what you're doing.
向けてほしけりゃ
もうちょっと有能になることだ
Well, it looks like he totally blew me off.
さてと…
随分 ナメられたもんだけど
But can you guys really do as he says?
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
あんたらは
お役に立てんのかしら？
"He was assaulted by them," says MISAKA says MISAKA stating the truth.
（ﾗｽﾄｵｰﾀﾞｰ）
この人たちに襲われたのって―
ミサカはミサカは
本当のことを言ってみる
But didn't your friend do all this?
（上条）
だけど これって お前の知り合いが
やったってことなのか？
"That's very unlikely."
（ﾗｽﾄｵｰﾀﾞｰ）
それはないかも
"He's short-tempered and really likes to fight."
（ﾗｽﾄｵｰﾀﾞｰ）
あの人は
気が短くて ケンカっ早いから―
仕返しが これっぽっちだなんて
考えられないもんって―
"So I don't think he would leave such a small mess behind,"
says MISAKA says MISAKA attempting some simple extrapolation.
ミサカはミサカは
簡単に推測してみたり
We have to call the police—
（上条）
とにかく通報しないと
ウワッ！
"They're here!" reports MISAKA reports MISAKA hiding herself behind the car.
（ﾗｽﾄｵｰﾀﾞｰ）ヤツらが来た
（上条）うん？
…て ミサカはミサカは 車の陰に
体を隠しながら報告してみたり
Who are they?
“ヤツら”？
（車の音）
Oh, what's this?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
おや？　こりゃ何だ？
（ｵｰｿﾝ）
うん？
ああ そりゃ嗅覚センサーだ
It's a scent sensor.
That's how we track our targets.
（ｵｰｿﾝ）そいつで標的のあとを追う
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）要は警察犬の機械化か
So it's a police dog machine.
But man, it's too quiet.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
しっかし この静けさは何だ？
Don't tell me this is another detail Kihara decided to include.
まさか これも
木原の演出ってんじゃねえだろうな
フフフン フフフン フンフン♪
And why the hell were you there?
お前 なんで
あんなとこ いやがったんだ？
うん？
借りてた物を返しに来たんだよ
I came back to return something.
Here, the newest in hygienic toiletries!
ほら！　この最新鋭日用品
Are you stupid?
バカか お前は
That's disposable.
こんな使い捨ての…
"And the duckling that everyone kept calling ugly was actually a sexy swan."
“ダメ子 ダメ子と
罵られていた醜いアヒルは―”
“実は 超エロカッコイイ
白鳥さんだったのでした”
"The end."
“おしまい”
Hey, what does "sexy" mean?
ねえ
“エロカッコイイ”って なに？
That's not how The Ugly Duckling goes.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
「みにくいアヒルの子」は
そういう話じゃねえよ
Then how does it go?
じゃ どんなお話？
はぁ？　つうか 何だっけか？
What was it, anyway?
According to that brat, it was something like the little swan was really happy
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
確か あのガキが言うには―
アヒルさんたちと
仲良くなりたかった白鳥は―
when he found out the truth that he can't join the ducklings' social circle even if he wanted to.
自分が彼らの輪に加われない事実を
突きつけられて―
本当に幸せだったのかな …だっけ
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）チッ…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）“あのガキ”って―
Is "that brat" the person you were looking for?
あなたが捜してた迷子の人のこと？
The one I'm still looking for.
正しくは
今も捜してるって状態だがな
You two got separated again?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
また はぐれちゃったの？
ああ そうだ
だから お前とは ここでお別れだ
Yeah.
That's why I have to say bye to you now.
I'll look for her with you!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）私も捜すよ
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）えっ？
I can tell it's a problem for you.
だって
あなたが困ってるの分かるもん
Touma would say the same thing.
当麻(とうま)だったら
同じこと言ってると思うし
フン…
Stop here.
この辺りで止めろ
There's a huge hospital around here.
この近くに でかい病院がある
Go there, and look for the frog-faced doctor.
そこに行って カエルに
よく似た顔の医者を見つけろ
Tell him to prepare a battery for the MISAKA Network connection terminal.
医者に会ったら―
“ミサカネットワーク接続用電極の
バッテリーを用意しろ”と伝えろ
He'll know what I mean.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）それで通じる
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん 分かった
Okay!
A battery for the MISAKA Network connection terminal.
ミサカネットワーク接続用電極の
バッテリーだね
Please wait here.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）待っててね
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）ああ？
I wouldn't like it if you went off without me.
私が戻ってくるまで
ちゃんと待ってなきゃヤダよ
Fine, just go.
分かってる
いいから さっさと行け
Keep moving.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
車を出せ
You still won't let me go?
まだ解放してくんねえのか？
Do you want to live or die?
死ぬか生きるか お前が選べよ
ハァハァ…
生きてるか？　ラストオーダー
Still alive, Last Order?!
Crap, it's closed.
ダメだ　閉まってる
"This might do something about it."
（ﾗｽﾄｵｰﾀﾞｰ）これなら外せるかも
（上条）あっ…
Let's go somewhere with a lot of people.
（上条）
とにかく 人の多い所へ行こう
連中は騒ぎを起こしたくないはずだ
They wouldn't want to cause a ruckus.
"I wonder if this can really save him," says MISAKA says MISAKA lamenting her lack of power.
こんなので 本当に あの人を
助けることなんてできるのかなって
ミサカはミサカは
自分の力のなさを嘆いてみたり
I dunno, but...
さあな
でも ここを生き延びないかぎり
絶対に助けられない
If we don't survive first, we'll never save him.
If you want to save him, make sure you don't die first.
そいつを助けたかったら
まずは自分が死なないことだ
"Okay," says MISAKA says MISAKA nodding in agreement.
うんって ミサカはミサカは
首を縦に振ってみる
All right, then. Let's go.
じゃ 生きるぞ
（ドアの開く音）
What's going on?
どうなってるんだ？
とにかく外に…
Let's head outside—
What sort of business do you have calling me this late?
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
こんな時間に どんな要件かな？
We have trouble. Big trouble.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
トラブルが起きた
でかいトラブルだ
I have the general idea of things from the little sister MISAKA.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
一応 御坂(みさか)妹さんとやらから―
大体の事情は聞いているよ
Apparently there's information transfer going on in their network right now.
彼女たちの
電気的ネットワークを介して―
情報の交換が行われているらしいね
Then I don't need to explain.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
だったら 話は早(はえ)え
Where's that brat?
あのガキは どうなってる？
It seems like she's being chased by another Hound Dog squad.
今は 猟犬部隊(ハウンドドッグ)の別動隊に
追われているようだね
Apparently she's with an ordinary person she happened to run into.
たまたま居合わせた一般人と
一緒だそうだけど
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
チッ… 場所は？
Where?
She doesn't seem to know herself.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
彼女自身もつかめていないようだね
Did a brat wearing a white sister outfit come your way?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
そっちに
白い修道服を着たガキは来たか？
Why does she know about your alternative calculation?
彼女 なんで君の代理演算のことを
知っているんだ？
That's none of your business.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
お前には関係ねえ
いいから そこへ引き止めとけ
Just keep her there.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
フゥ… やれやれ…
Good grief.
How far are you planning to go with this?
それで
君は どこまでやるつもりだい？
I'll kill Kihara.
木原は殺す　猟犬部隊(ハウンドドッグ)もつぶす
I'll crush Hound Dog.
And I'll save that brat without a scratch on her.
そして あのガキを無傷で助け出す
Impossible.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
不可能だよ
You have too many objectives in your current situation.
この状況の中で―
君は あまりに多くの行動目標を
抱え過ぎている
You won't be able to achieve them all.
それでは絶対に達成できない
You're a doctor, what the hell do you—
知ったような口利くな！
いつから医者が…
I've seen hell, places far worse than you know.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
僕は
君以上の地獄を見てきているよ
だからこそ言えることもある
That's why I can say these things, Accelerator.
アクセラレータ　君は
余計でムダな高望みなどせず―
Don't shoot for the targets you can't hit.
Just make Last Order's safety your top priority.
ラストオーダーの命を
助けることだけを優先しろ
If you bring her to me alive I will cure her, no questions asked.
生きて僕のもとまで連れてくれば
必ず治す
Making sure that happens is what a doctor is about.
その期待に応えるのが
医者ってもんだ
フフッ…
上等じゃねえか
Fair enough.
Must be God's Right Seat.
（土御門(つちみかど)）
神の右席か
I didn't think they'd go this far.
（土御門）
まさか ここまでやるとはな
Yomikawa to HQ.
（黄泉川(よみかわ)）
こちら 黄泉川から本部へ
コール334についての詳細を求める
Requesting details on Call 334.
This woman...
この女…
な …んだ？
What... the...
Resource Recycling Center Number 3.
（ﾛｯﾄﾞ）
第３資源再生処理施設か
The target's scent leads inside.
（ﾅﾝｼｰ）
標的のにおいは
あっちへ続いているわ
This has to be it.
まず間違いないでしょうね
If you want to go home safely, you'd better stay calm.
無事に帰りたかったら
おとなしくしてるこった
うん？　“洗浄剤”　これだな
A cleaning product...?
Found it.
I guess I'll wipe my scent then get out of here.
さっさと においを消して
こっから立ち去るとするか
Shit.
くそったれが
予想よりも早いじゃねえか
They're faster than I thought.
（美琴(みこと)）
う～ん… 小さいのしかないのか
They only have small ones?
Onee-sama!
（黒子(くろこ)）お姉様！
（美琴）何よ？　黒子
What do you want, Kuroko?
I'm going to be home late because of some Judgment work.
（黒子）
風紀委員(ジャッジメント)のお仕事で帰れないので
Could you let that annoying dorm mistress know for me?
あのやかましい寮監に 門限延長の
連絡をしてほしいんですの
It's way past curf—
（黒子）もう門限も過ぎて…
（美琴）え～っと…―
Um, I'm actually out at the convenience store.
私も今 コンビニだから
I didn't think Onee-sama would be out as well...
（黒子）
お姉様まで外出中だなんて…
これで
問答無用で減点を食らいそうですの
We're going to get minus points for sure now.
（初春(ういはる)）
御坂さん 今日は なんで
門限ぶっちぎっているんでしょうね
I wonder why Misaka-san is out past curfew tonight.
ハッ… ま… まさか
D-Don't tell me...
あのまま お姉様は
腐れ類人猿と夜のデート？
Onee-sama is out on an evening date with that monkey bastard?!
Damn it!
おのれ！
あの野郎 雨の夜景を楽しむなんて
また随分と渋いチョイスを
He's got good taste, I'll give him that; asking her out to see the rain this evening.
こうしては いられませんわ
There's no other choice.
It is my duty to protect Onee-sama's chastity!
お姉様の貞操を守るのは
私 白井(しらい)黒子の務め！
ダメですよ
ほら こっちの事務書類と―
You can't.
There's still a mountain of paperwork we haven't finished yet.
会計書類の山が
全然 終わってないでしょう？
What the hell is going on?
どういう状況だ？
なぜ仕掛けてこない？
Why aren't they coming?
Hi!
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）ハ～イ！
（上条）ハッ…
Did I surprise you?
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
びっくりしちゃったかな？
怖がってないで 出ておいで
こっちにも事情があるからさ
There's no need to be scared, just come on out.
I have other work I need to do, you know.
So, if you don't listen to me,
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
あんまり言うこと聞いてくんないと
I'm gonna beat you to a pulp!
グッチャグチャの塊にすんぞ
こらぁ！
ウワッ！
Who the hell are you?
お前は…
One from God's Right Seat, Vento of the Front.
神の右席のひとり　前方のヴェント
Target acquired.
目標発見
Now then, Kamijou Touma, I'm gonna kill you!
そんなわけで
さっさとぶっ殺されろ 上条当麻！
（ﾅﾝｼｰ）ロッド 嗅覚センサーは？
（ﾛｯﾄﾞ）待て　今 終わる
Rod, what's the scent sensor saying?
Hang on, it's still analyzing.
Come on, there's no reason to be scared.
緊張しなくても大丈夫だよ
痛みなんて感じる暇もないんだから
I won't give you the chance to feel any pain.
（激突音）
隠れてろ ラストオーダー
Find somewhere to hide, Last Order!
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）アハハッ…
（上条）ハッ…
ハハッ！　さすがはウワサの右手
よく頑張って ついてくるわね
So that's the infamous right hand of yours.
Good job keeping up with me!
上か！
From above?
（上条）アア…
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）楽しい！
This is so much fun!
なるほど なるほど！
I see, I see!
その右手 報告にあったとおり
効き目抜群みたいね
Just like the reports state, that right hand of yours is extraordinary!
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
ところどころに織り交ぜてる―
My favorite "attack from all directions" is totally ineffective!
私の本命が全く効いてないわ
（上条）
本命？
Favorite?
Alas, I don't understand a thing about it.
しっかし
こんだけじゃ よく分かんないし
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）よし　試してみっか
（上条）てめえ！
Well, let's try this then.
You bitch!
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
はぁ～… そうなってんのね
Hmm. I see, I see.
My bad!
すんません！　なんか 痛みを
感じる暇もなくってのはムリみたい
I guess I can't finish you off painlessly.
だから 幸せになりたかったら
マゾにでも目覚めてね
So, if you truly wish to be happy, try becoming a masochist.
Why have those attacks not come from the same direction as her hammer swing?
さっきから ハンマーの動きと
攻撃がズレてやがる
Could it be...
まさか その十字架…
that cross?!
Oh, man! You found out?
や～ん！　バレちゃった？
Shit!
くそ！
Okay, this is starting to get bothersome.
あら… なんだか
面倒くさくなってきちゃったな
ほい！
ウワッ！　ウウッ…
（上条）逃げろ！
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）フッ…
Run!
Go! Please!
行け！
頼む 助けを呼んできてくれ
Find someone who can help!
Forget it!
（上条）拾うな！
（ﾗｽﾄｵｰﾀﾞｰ）あっ…
That's pretty cold.
あんたって残酷ね
あんな小さな子供に
暗闇の中を逃げ続けさせるなんて
How could you make a little girl run around the streets at night?
一緒に殺してあげたほうが
幸せなんじゃないの？
Wouldn't it be better if you two died together?
She'll be fine once I go after her.
俺が迎えに行けば 問題ねえ
だから 俺は死なない
That's why I'm not going to die here.
That sounds fun.
あら 楽しい
でもでも
五臓六腑(ごぞうろっぷ)を人肉ジュースにしても
But do you really think you'll say the same thing after I turn your guts into human juice?
同じセリフ言えるかしら？
まあ
こっちの標的は あんたなわけだし
Well, whatever. You're my only target.
And I can't thank you enough for deciding not to run away!
逃げないってんなら
大助かりなんだけどさ！
じょ… 冗談でしょう？
Y-You've gotta be kidding me...
"Kidding you"? I guess so.
冗談？　そうだなぁ… 新ネタだ
It's a new routine.
What a shame.
悪いな　誰 敵に回したか
分かってんのか？　お前
Don't you know who you were messing with?
（上条）ハァハァ…
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）優しいわね
Well aren't you the kind one.
自分の心配しなくていいのかしら？
But do you really have time to be watching out for others?
You bitch!
（上条）てめえ！
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）フフッ…
What are you going to do now that you're mad?
今更 熱くなって どうすんのよ？
Surely you know what kind of situation Academy City is in.
学園都市が今 どうなってるか
分かってんでしょう？
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
自分の価値に気づきなさいな
You need to realize your own worth.
My objective is you, Kamijou Touma.
私の目的は上条当麻
それ以外は全部 おまけ
Anything else is just extra.
Even that Index is insignificant compared to you.
あの禁書目録ですら
あんたに比べりゃ軽いってことよ
Right now, you are unquestionably an enemy of the Roman Catholic Church.
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
今のあんたは
間違いなくローマ正教の敵
And we use any means necessary to defeat our enemies.
そして 我々は
どんな手を使ってでも敵を倒す
Even if it means the eradication of all of Japan.
日本という一国家を
消滅させてでもね
As you can see, the Pope himself signed it.
このとおり
ローマ教皇じきじきのサイン付き
What are you talking about?
（上条）どういうことだ？
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）冗談に聞こえるかな？
You think I'm joking?
I'll start by killing everyone in this store, then!
そんじゃ これから
店内にいる人間全員を殺す
ンッ… やめろ！
Stop!
Let's do this!
吹っ飛べ こらぁ！
Vera here. Requesting an update.
（ｳﾞｪｰﾗ）
こちら ヴェーラ
状況の報告を　オーバー
Over.
（無線:ノイズ）
くそ！
Damn it!
（ｳﾞｪｰﾗ）
ハッ… ナンシー？
Nancy?!
（血の滴る音）
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）くそ…
Shit...
何だ？　魔術の副作用か？
What?
Is this a side effect of her magic?
Hey, Shirai-san!
（初春）
白井さん
Which bento do you want?
お弁当 どっちにします？
中華丼と…
There's chop suey and there's fish bento.
Right now, that monkey and Onee-sama are strolling through the evening streets...
今 この瞬間も お姉様と
腐れ類人猿は一緒に夜の街を…
Oh, the variety show I always watch is about to start!
あっ 「いきなりバラエティー」の
時間です　テレビ テレビ…
TV, TV...
（黒子）
中華！
I don't care!
（ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ）
現在 学園都市で
侵入者騒動が起きているそうです
We're getting reports of intruder riots in Academy City.
（初春）うん？
（ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ）それに伴い―
Various locations within the city have suffered widespread damage.
学園都市内各地でも
被害が拡大しているとのことです
あっ 映像が入りました
Oh, we're getting the video now.
Please standby
Did they just say there's an intruder?
さっきの映像
こっちに報告 来てましたっけ？
でも 本当に たったひとりで
警備員(アンチスキル)を圧倒してるとしたら―
The intruder must be really powerful, taking out Anti-skill members alone...
あの侵入者
危険度はハンパじゃないですよ
If the situation worsens, an assistance request would be sent by Anti-skill.
（黒子）
ホントにマズければ
警備員(アンチスキル)から 応援要請が来ますわよ
それまでに書類をできるだけ…
Until then, we can only handle the paperwork as best we can.
（黒子）
えっ？　初春？
Uiharu?
That should take care of any scent traces I left.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
こいつで連中の嗅覚を振り切れる
あれか
There you are.
H-Help me! That's the guy that did it!
（ﾛｯﾄﾞ）助けろ　俺を保護してくれ
（警備員たち）うん？
ハハッ…
ざまあみろ！　俺は助かった！
Sucks to be you, I'm saved now!
手ぇ出しゃ
さんざん守りたがっていた―
Your days of protecting that little brat are over now!
クソガキとの関係も―
終わりだぜ
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）ウオーッ！
（警備員）ハッ… 何の声だ？
What the...
（警備員）
な… 何だ？
Wait! Stop, please, Accelerator!
（ﾛｯﾄﾞ）
待て！ 待ってくれ アクセラレータ
助け…
Help m—
S-Step away from that man!
そ… その人から離れろ
シュールな光景だ
This is one bizarre scene.
ンッ… なるほど
I see.
So this is how they plan to attack Academy City.
学園都市も こうやって
攻撃していくつもりだったのか
They're going to skewer everyone while they're paralyzed.
動けない人間を
ひとりひとり串刺しにしていくと
This is pretty bad.
マズイな
Aiho!
（芳川(よしかわ)）
愛穂(あいほ)！　あっ…
（無線）第５学区内
（芳川）あっ…
We've compared evidence from the crime scene at District 5 with the one from the databanks,
事件現場での証言を基に
バンクより照合
and are releasing a search order for this person on charges of attempted murder.
この者を殺人未遂事件の
重要参考人として手配する
～♪
Next Episode
People are collapsing one after another.
（上条）
次々と倒れる人たち
Accelerator notices the strange events occurring in Academy City.
学園都市の不穏な動きに
アクセラレータは咆哮(ほうこう)する
And a huge pair of wings soars through the heavens.
そして 天空に舞う巨大な翼
まさか それは…
No way, is that...
Next time: "Testament."
次回 「学習装置(テスタメント)」
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる